limboland.net 2016-06-24

# Privacy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Last Updated: July 4, 2014

Limbo Vision, Inc. and SEODominators.com strives to offer its visitors the  many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject  to the terms of this privacy policy.

How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting,  the activities in which you elect to participate and the services  provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you  register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain  features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may  provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests,  message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site.  Like most Web sites, Limboland.net and SEODominators.com also collects  information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that  may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of  your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie  may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to  re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our  site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information  through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us  with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to  accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain  portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and  password, and we may not be able to customize the sites features  according to your preferences.  
 **  
What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and  deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your  privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be  used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your  usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to  help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are  visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated  Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally  Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you  individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information  collected on Limboland.net or SEODominators.com to communicate with you  about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of  Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by Our Company and websites and other topics we think you might find of interest. 

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Limbo Vision, Inc. may also be  used for other purposes, including but not limited to site  administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions,  administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications  with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the  operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access  such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business,  we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses.  In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred  assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court  order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do  so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to  us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it  appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

 **Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements** Limbo Vision, Inc. expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to  respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content  providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and  data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit  to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on one or more  of our pages, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a  third party. Also, through Limboland.net and or SEODominators.com you  may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites,  features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Limbo  Vision, Inc. is not responsible for the actions or policies of such  third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated  by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to  attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information  about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third  parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine  whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features  available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and  may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Limbo Vision, Inc. does not control the use of this technology by third parties or  the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or  policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if  you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message  boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may  result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties.  Such activities are beyond the control of Limbo Vision, Inc. and this  policy. **

Children

**  
Limbo Vision, Inc. Limboland.net  and or SEODominators.com does not knowingly collect or solicit  Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13  except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any  information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will  delete that information immediately. If you believe Limbo Vision, Inc.  has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at  the address listed below. **

Contacting Us

**

Limbo Vision, Inc.  
(DBA Limboland.net)  
(DBA SEODominators.com)  
9911 mammoth Dr.  
Huntington Beach, CA 92646  
phone (714) 968-7697

john @ limboland.net  

 **Changes to this Policy

Limbo Vision, Inc. reserves the right to change this policy at any time.  Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of  our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you  accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at  the time the information was collected.

Governing law

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by California law. If a  dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it  with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following  location: Orange County, California, USA. Any costs and fees other than  attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by  each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually  satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute  to binding arbitration at the following location: Orange County,  California, USA, under the rules of the American Arbitration  Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be  entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

Limbo Vision,  Inc. is operated and administered entirely within California. This  statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do  not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any  party.

**

© Copyright 2014 Limbo Vision, Inc. (All rights reserved)
